[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What night club is Laura the host of in the film The Last Dragon?", "correct_answer": "7th Heaven", "incorrect_answers": ["Harlem Nights", "Night Moves", "Legends"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Komodo Dragon is only one of 3 species of venomous lizards in the world.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Octopuses have excellent vision. Which of the following statements about an octopuss vision is NOT true?", "correct_answer": "They can see in color.", "incorrect_answers": ["They can see well at night.", "They can see in depth.", "They can make out size and shape very well."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Leibniz Calculator was invented in 1692.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This endangered turtle is the biggest of all living turtles, reaching a length of over 2.7 m (8.8 ft) and weight of 900 kg (2,000 lb).", "correct_answer": "Leatherback Sea Turtle", "incorrect_answers": ["Kemps Ridley Turtle", "Hawksbill Sea Turtle", "Mesoamerican River Turtle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the nervous system regulates involuntary actions such as heartbeat or digestion?", "correct_answer": "autonomic nervous system", "incorrect_answers": ["central nervous system", "peripheral nervous system", "involuntary nervous system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Low-fat foods contain very little if any sugar.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following brands of beer is not German and is manufactured in an Asian country?", "correct_answer": "Kirin", "incorrect_answers": ["Jever", "Veltins", "Holsten"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Everglades National Park is located in this US state.", "correct_answer": "Florida", "incorrect_answers": ["Hawaii", "Nevada", "Georgia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which girls name is also a the name of a computer programming language?", "correct_answer": "Ada", "incorrect_answers": ["Amelia", "Anna", "Agnes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first rock group to play at New Yorks Carnegie Hall?", "correct_answer": "Chicago", "incorrect_answers": ["America", "The Who", "The Beatles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This perennial herb was once used to make absinthe.", "correct_answer": "Wormwood", "incorrect_answers": ["Muscal Buttons", "Mandrake", "Woodruff"]}]